《指定幸存者》前情提要...
"Designated Survivor"...
麦克利什拒绝众议院议长之职
MacLeish turned down Speaker of the House.
副总统怎么样
What about the Vice Presidency?
我不胜荣幸
I would be honored.
麦克利什  副总统人选
MacLeish? For VP?
他们要开始忠贞审查了
They want to start the vetting.
我有消息称
I have a source claiming
李奥·柯克曼不是总统的亲生儿子
that Leo Kirkman is not the president's son.
抓到马吉德·纳萨尔了
We have Majid Nassar.
审讯出结果需要时间
Effective interrogation takes time.
给你24小时
You've got 24 hours.
你在不知道对方是谁的情况下
You signed on to this,
就这么贸然地加入了他的行动吗
and you don't know the person who set you up?
他说他叫卡特兰
He said his name was Catalan.
如果你告诉任何人  他也会杀了你
If you tell anyone, he'll kill you, too.
-什么事  -纳萨尔
- What is it? - Nassar.
发现他这样了
And I found him like this.
我要接触过食物的人员名单
I want the name of every single person
一个都不能漏
that came in contact with that food.
做毒性检测  查DNA
I want tox, I want DNA,
给我找到指纹
I want fingerprints.
给我找到监控视频
I want video-camera surveillance footage.
每一份调查的结果都给我
Every single result comes to me.
来把事情捋一捋
Still wrapping things up.
在纳萨尔说出真相之前
Whoever blew up the Capitol must have murdered Nassar
炸国会大厦的人就把纳萨尔杀掉了
before he told anyone else the truth.
杰森  他告诉我们了
He told us, Jason.
我知道
I know.
但那对我们现在有什么用
But what good does that do us now?
我们没有证据
We have no proof.
所以我们要加紧调查
Which is why we need to press on
纳萨尔留给我们的唯一线索
with the only lead Nassar gave us.
-没错  -好的
- Yeah. - All right.
-中尉在外面  -小心后面
- Lieutenant's outside. - Watch your back.
但如果他只告诉了我们卡特兰的话
But if we're the only ones that he told about Catalan,
他们迟早会找到我们
it's only a matter of time before they come for us.
指定幸存者
第一季 第七集
翻译：   sienna  wdjmhs  长颈鹿  天青月白
■
当纽约洋基队在911事件一周之后开始比赛
When the New York Yankees took the field a week after 9/11,
翻译：  silence  Michael  桃子  星星与野狗
他们让我们把生活继续下去
they allowed us to move forward with our lives.
是体育精神让我们重新站起来
It was sports, not speeches,
校对： 彼岸的宁静   持久
而不是演讲
that allowed us to get back on our feet.
所以当我听到我们的运动健儿要赶赴莫斯科
So when I heard that our athletes were going to Moscow
时间轴：   AVis   姜姜
参加国际田径锦标赛的时候
to compete in the International Track and Field Championships,
我想亲自谢谢他们
I wanted to thank them myself.
后期：虫虫不咬人    总监：小早
威斯顿教练
Coach Weston.
总统先生  这是我们的荣幸
It's an honor, Mr. President.
我们都为此感到骄傲
We're extremely proud.
尤其是在我们的国家刚经历过磨难之后
Especially after what our nation's been through.
是我的荣幸
The honor is mine.
威斯顿教练  给对手好好露一手
Coach Weston,show them what we've got.
你一定总听人这么说
You must get this all the time,
回想1992年  当你打破400米
but back in '92, when you broke the world record
世界纪录的时候
for the 400 meters,
那是我所见过的最难以置信的事情
that was one of the most incredible things I'd ever seen.
谢谢  总统先生
I appreciate that, Mr. President.
打扰一下  总统先生
Excuse me, Mr. President.
麦克利什议员和他妻子到了
Congressman MacLeish and his wife have arrived.
谢谢你  怀特
Thank you, Wyatt.
对不起  我得先离开一下
I'm sorry. I have to step away.
见到你真是高兴
It was a pleasure to meet you.
总统先生  请记住
Remember, Mr. President --
领导者是时势造就的  非天生的
Leaders are made, not born.
-我们都支持你  -谢谢
- We're rooting for you, sir. - Thank you.
我不知道我当时吃了什么
I don't know what it was I ate,
但是无论是什么  我当时吐得厉害
but whatever it was, I was sick as a dog.
让我猜一猜
And let me guess.
他一直很绅士地帮你把头发挽在后面
Like a gentleman, he held your hair back the whole time.
没有  他给我叫了一辆出租车
No. He put me in a cab on my own,
然后他回餐厅了
and he went back into the restaurant,
他在那里坐到他们勒令厨房停止营业为止
and he sat there until they shut the kitchen down
这样就不会有其他人生病了
so that no one else would get sick.
那时我就知道...
And that is when I knew...
我会是一个很好的卫生检查员
That I would be a good health inspector.
你们呢
How about you guys?
你们怎么认识的
H-How did you first meet?
我们在大学认识的
We met in college.
我姐妹会朋友有一天来我家跟我说
My sorority sister came home one day and said,
"我要给你介绍一个完美的男人"
"I have the perfect guy for you.
"他又帅又幽默"
He's cute. He is funny."
那是...
Mm-hmm. And that was...
我室友
My roommate.
那人对我没兴趣
Who could not have been less interested in me.
我才不信这话
I don't believe that.
为了减轻对我的打击  他把彼得介绍给我了
Well, to soften the blow, he introduced me to Peter.
我觉得是我室友的判断失误
I like to think I reaped the benefits
才让我捡了个大便宜
of my roommate's poor judgment.
你认为怎么样
How do you think it's going?
答案跟你十分钟前问的一样
Well, probably the same as when you asked 10 minutes ago.
第一场比赛回来  奇才队就已经乱炸了
First game back, the Wizards are already bombing.
对不起  不该说炸这个字
I'm sorry. Poor choice of words.
说真的  我们再也找不到
I'm telling you -- We're never gonna find
一个比麦克利什更适合副总统一职的候选人了
a better candidate for Vice President than MacLeish.
你知道  我也知道
You know that. I know that.
但总统此前从未处理过这些事
But POTUS has never been in this position before.
他想周全些
He wants to be thorough.
我只是希望我们能够快些推进这一环节
I just wish we could fast-forward to the part
好让我们给这个国家一点好消息
where we give the country some good news for once.
尤其是选举就快到了
Especially with elections coming up.
不
No!
沃尔不能这么打球
Wall can't play through that one!
他该让波特或者比尔协攻
He's got to get Porter or Beal involved.
波特挡拆晚了
Porter was late filling the lane.
什么
What?
不光只有男的喜欢运动
Men don't own sports.
亚伦·肖尔
Aaron Shore.
是
Yeah.
好  谢谢您
Yeah. Thank you.
我马上告知他
I'll let him know.
该死
Damn it.
怎么了
What is it?
亚伦  我需要五分钟跟总统谈谈
Hey, Aaron, I need five minutes with the president.
是私事
It's personal.
总统今晚不处理私事
The president's not doing personal tonight.
介意我问一个问题吗
Do you mind if I ask a question?
当然不介意  问吧
Sure. Go ahead.
我只是很好奇
I-I -- I guess I'm just curious
住在这里是种什么感觉
what it's like really living here,
您知道的  就是家人  婚姻都在监控之下
you know, with your family and your marriage, the scrutiny.
我们也还在适应
We're still trying to figure that out.
不好意思  打扰一下
Sorry to interrupt.
总统先生  我们能私下谈谈吗
Mr. President, may I have a word, please?
当然
Of course.
失陪一下
Will you excuse me?
那你的室友现在去哪里了
So, where is the roommate now?
马吉德·纳萨尔死了
Majid Nassar is dead?
这怎么可能呢
How the hell is that even possible?
他在我们羁押之下
He was in our custody.
调查局正在查
FBI's investigating.
说他在牢房里被投毒
They say - he was poisoned in his cell.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
我能让亚特伍德副局长在一小时内
I can get Deputy Director Atwood here within the hour
-来做简报  -马上去办
- for a briefing. - Do it -- now.
亚伦
Aaron.
不要走漏半点风声
Not a word of this to anyone.
直到我们搞清楚状况
Not until we have some answers.
太抱歉了
I am so sorry.
这件事比预想的要麻烦
This is gonna take longer than I had hoped.
不必道歉的
Oh no, no. Don't apologize.
我们理解  这是职责所在
We understand. Duty calls.
总统先生  我知道自己还不是副总统
Mr. President, I know I'm not VP yet,
也许将来也不会
and maybe I never will be,
但如果我能帮您
but if there's ever anything I can do
减轻一些负担
to help you ease your burden,
我希望您随时吩咐
I hope - you won't hesitate to ask.
谢谢你  彼得
Thank you, Peter.
再次表示歉意  失陪了
Again, I am so sorry. Excuse me.
好  没问题
Yeah, of course.
好的
All right.
总统要听纳萨尔谋杀的情况汇报
The president wants a briefing on the Nassar murder.
-现在吗  -是的
- Now? - Yeah.
你得把我们掌握的所有情况都告诉他
Okay, you need to tell him -- everything we know.
总统想让我汇报的
The president is expecting me to brief him
是一起谋杀的调查
on a murder investigation.
如果我突然抛出对麦克利什的揣测
He's gonna think I'm crazy if I blindside him
他会以为我疯了
with theories about MacLeish.
这不是揣测
They're not theories.
纳萨尔与袭击的关联远不及彼得·麦克利什
Peter MacLeish has closer ties to the attack than Nassar ever did,
而且我们有证据
and we have evidence of that.
用不了多久
It is only a matter of time
他与总统宝座就会仅有一步之遥
before he's a heartbeat away from the presidency.
柯克曼得知道这一点
Kirkman needs to know that.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
好运
Good luck.
总统可以见您了  先生
The president's ready for you, sir.
总统先生
Mr. President.
谢谢  怀特
Thank you, Wyatt.
副局长  希望你已经查出结果了
Deputy Director, please tell me that you've got some answers.
的确有  先生
I believe I do, sir.
这是好消息
That's good news.
麦克利什议员
Congressman MacLeish.
我没想到你也在
I wasn't expecting to see you.
议员先生是
The congressman has served
反恐与国土安全委员会的成员
on the Subcommittee for Terrorism and Homeland Security.
鉴于目前情况  我认为让他列席
Given the circumstances, I felt it was appropriate
比较合适
that he joined us tonight.
当然没问题
Yes, of course.
纳萨尔到底是怎么回事
What the hell happened with Nassar?
我们目前还没有太多信息
Well, we don't have much intel at the moment,
但我保证会调查一切可能性
but I promise you we're looking into every possibility.
他死前交代什么了吗
Did we get anything out of him before he died?
他不是很配合
He wasn't very cooperative.
我知道他不配合
I get - that he wasn't cooperative.
你要我授权你们审问他
You asked for the authority to interrogate him.
我授权了
I gave it to you.
我以为你有办法
I assumed - you knew what you were doing.
抱歉  总统先生
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
我也希望有更多信息
I wish I could say more.
副局长  您进门时说
Deputy Director, when you walked in,
你认为你查出了结果
you said you thought you had answers.
我是说我们还在继续努力
I meant that we are still working on it.
好吧
Fine.
就到这里吧
That'll be all.
有真正进展以后再来找我
Get back to me when you've actually got something.
明白  先生
Yes, sir.
总统先生
Mr. President.
议员先生
Congressman.
这讲不通
That didn't make any sense.
总统先生  我相信联调局
Oh, Mr. President, I have to believe the FBI
会尽一切所能调查此事
is doing everything they can to solve this.
我相信你是对的
I'm sure you're right.
这都快成习惯了
This is becoming a habit.
我记得以前都是你半夜醒来看到我在工作
I remember when you used to wake up to me working.
相信我  我还是喜欢以前那样
Trust me, - I liked it better that way.
怎么回事
What's going on?
你是否有过奇怪的直觉
You ever get that weird feeling
认为有人在对你撒谎
when you think someone's lying to you?
你当然有过
Of course you do.
-你是律师  -你说的是谁
- You're a lawyer. - Who are you thinking?
杰森·亚特伍德
Jason Atwood.
联调局副局长
Deputy Director, FBI.
你为什么觉得他在撒谎
Why do you think he's lying?
说不清楚
Can't say exactly.
我只是感觉有什么事不对劲
I just have this feeling that something's not right.
亚特伍德执意要审问马吉德·纳萨尔
Atwood pressed me really hard to interrogate Majid Nassar.
12小时后  纳萨尔死了
12 hours later, Nassar's dead.
纳萨尔却什么答案也没找到
Atwood can't answer a single question about how or why.
我只是觉得不对劲
It just doesn't feel right.
我接手一件案子
Well, when I'm trying a case,
只会讲有证据的部分
I only bring up what I can prove.
亚特伍德不会把无凭无据的事
Atwood's not gonna give you any answers
作为答案告诉你
that he can't stand behind.
再给他一些时间吧
I'd just give him some time.
早安  总统先生
Morning, Mr. President.
你睡得好吗
Did you get any sleep?
我确信那间卧室见证了很多事
I'm sure that bedroom's seen a lot of things,
但睡个好觉肯定不在其中之列
but I don't think a good night's sleep is one of them.
我要你持续跟进纳萨尔的调查
Look, I need you to stay on top of the Nassar investigation.
利用我们整个情报体系中可调动的资源
Use every resource our intelligence community has to offer.
没问题  先生
Absolutely, sir.
-早上好  怀特  -早上好  总统先生
- Good morning, Wyatt. - Good morning, Mr. President.
总统先生  驻俄大使
Mr. President, I just got off the phone
刚刚来过电话
with our ambassador in Russia.
威斯顿教练刚到莫斯科就被逮捕了
Coach Weston was arrested upon landing in Moscow.
什么  什么指控
What? On what charges?
海关他在包里搜出20瓶生长激素
Customs found 20 vials of HGH in his bag.
他们说他为自己的运动员
They're saying that he's been supplying his athletes
提供兴奋剂
with - performance-enhancing drugs.
俄国人还有脸说吗
And the Russians are complaining?
太讽刺了  我不相信
That's ironic. I don't believe it.
无论真假  美国队的领队
Whether it's true or not, the head of the U.S.A. team
在国外被逮捕
was arrested on foreign soil.
这是件令国家蒙羞的丑闻
This is a national embarrassment.
国务院必须给他委派一名律师
The State Department needs to get him a lawyer.
已有一名律师受托前往
They're sending one over right now.
我要马上与他们谈话
I want to talk to them right away.
我昨晚说的话要算数
I meant what I said last night.
-威斯顿是位民族英雄  -好  总统先生
- Coach Weston is a national hero. - Yes, sir.
如果总统要解雇我  我也不会意外
I wouldn't be surprised if the president tried to fire me.
麦克利什就站在旁边
How the hell am I gonna talk about MacLeish
我该如何告诉总统关于他的疑点
if MacLeish is standing right there?
我要尽快再安排一次会面
I got to get another meeting as soon as possible.
卡特兰那边查得怎么样了
Where are we with Catalan?
恐怖分子数据库及国际刑警组织均一无所获
TIDE and Interpol came up with nothing.
监视名单上唯一相关的是一名西班牙激进分子
The only hits on any watch lists are old Spanish radicals.
你查了特别指定国民名单吗
Did you run him as a specially designated national?
查不到任何东西
Nothing.
我们要怎样才能取得进展
How the hell are we gonna get lucky?
中情局掌握的信息并非全部都会
Well, not everything the CIA knows
上传到恐怖分子身份数据库中
comes up on the TIDE database, so...
-你有线人  -是的
- You got a source? - I do.
今天下午我会与他见面
I'm gonna see him this afternoon.
只是他还不知道而已
He just doesn't know it yet.
一旦威斯顿与大使馆委派的律师见面
Let me know as soon as Weston
请立即知会我
speaks with the lawyers from the embassy.
这是总统指定的最高要务
This is a top priority for the president.
我真的要见一下总统
Hey, I really need that five minutes with the president.
现在可不行  赛斯
Now is not a good time, Seth.
-一位全民偶像即将锒铛入狱  -我知道
- A national icon's on his way to the Gulag. - Yeah, fully aware.
有50位记者等着我对此事置评呢
I have 50 reporters waiting for me to comment on that.
但我真的需要和他谈谈
But I really need to talk to him.
我已经和你说了  总统现在没时间
I told you the president has no time for
处理私人事宜
personal requests right now.
你不明白  这不是我的私人事宜
Look, you don't understand. This is not me personal.
这是总统的私人事宜
This is POTUS personal.
那晚我认识的那位叫丽萨的记者
That reporter I met the other night, Lisa...
她有一篇报道需要我置评
She needs a comment on a story.
-什么报道  -几天前
- What story? - A couple of days ago,
有一位刑事辩护律师来找她
she says a criminal-defense lawyer came to see her.
并和她说  他的匿名当事人
He says that his client, who he will not name,
是李奥的生父
is Leo's biological father.
好吧
All right.
你现在可以去和总统谈五分钟
You can have your five minutes now.
是真的吗
Is it true?
他叫杰弗里·迈尔斯
His name is Jeffrey Myers.
我与艾丽克斯相识时  他们在恋爱中
Alex was seeing him when we met.
我们在一起前  他们就分手了
She broke it off right before we started dating.
当艾丽克斯知道自己怀孕时
When we found out Alex was pregnant,
受孕时间令她惊慌
the timing of that scared her.
她问我是否要去做个血缘鉴定
She asked me if I wanted to take a test.
我拒绝了  因为这不会改变什么
I said no. Nothing would change.
我很爱她
I loved her.
好的方面是  没有做过亲子鉴定的话
Well, the good thing is, without a paternity test,
他们就没有实质性证据
they don't have anything concrete.
他不需要证据
He doesn't need it.
一旦故事开始流传  在得到公开答复之前
Once the story goes public, it's gonna raise questions
问题将一直存在
that won't go away until they're answered.
品牌广告推广合作  普罗米修斯  plmxs2016@gmail.com
他因什么入狱
What's he in prison for?
他在两年前因逃税被判有罪
He was convicted two years ago of felony tax evasion.
五年有期徒刑
Five-year sentence.
逃税吗  他逃了多少税
For tax evasion? How much was he hiding?
4600万美元
$46 million.
赛斯  这位记者...
Seth, this reporter...
《纪事报》的丽萨·乔丹
Lisa Jordan from the Chronicle.
-是的  她想要什么  -表态
- Right. What does she want? - A comment.
品牌广告推广合作  普罗米修斯  plmxs2016@gmail.com
我可以拖住她一会
I can hold her off,
但恐怕拖不了多久
but I don't have any ground to stand on.
这件事丝毫没有牵涉到国家安全
The story doesn't have any national-security implications.
是的  只涉及家庭问题
No. Just family ones.
尽你所能拖着她
Hold her off as long as you can.
我不想艾丽克斯和李奥突然被此事打击
I don't want Alex and Leo getting blindsided by this.
总统先生
Sir...
干什么
What?
总统先生  第一夫人已经知道
Well, sir, the... the first lady already knows
迈尔斯干的事了
that Myers has been talking.
-什么  -一个礼拜前  我们谈过此事
- What? A week ago. - We were talking about it,
她向我保证会和你说的
and she promised me that she would talk to you.
你知道那疯迈尔斯一个礼拜前
You knew that son of a bitch Myers
就开始散播消息却没有告诉我
was making noise a week ago, and you didn't tell me?
我该什么时候告诉你
Oh, w... when was I supposed to do that?
抓捕马吉德·纳萨尔时
Between Majid Nassar,
还是州长们要挟你时...
uh, the governors holding you hostage...
得了吧  艾丽克斯  这不公平
Come on, Alex. That's not fair.
我们说好了
We have a deal.
无论我们之间有什么事  都要优先考虑孩子
No matter what's happening with us, our children come first.
你怎敢这么怨我
Don't you dare throw that at me.
我这辈子全身心地保护着他们
My whole life has been about protecting them,
尤其当下
especially now.
17年来我们一直保护着李奥不让他知道此事
17 years trying to shield Leo from this.
而搬来白宫后一个月就功亏一篑
All it took was a month in the White House to undo it.
可能一开始不让李奥知情就是个错误
Maybe the mistake was keeping it from him in the first place.
-赛斯能为我们争取一些时间  -多久
- Seth thinks he can buy us some time. - Time?
即使他可以为我们争取到一辈子的时间
He can get us all the time in the world.
也无法抹去此事
This is not gonna go away.
你现在是总统了
You are the president now.
不如让我去找迈尔斯谈谈
Why don't I try and talk to Myers,
看看能否说通他
see if I can fix this?
不不  这不是个好主意
No, no. That's not a good idea.
那你有更好的主意吗
Well, do you have a better one?
干什么
What?!
怎么了
What is it?
代理国务卿帕尔森
Acting Secretary of State Paulsen
-和詹姆斯·卡莱拉来见您了  -为什么
- has brought James Carrera with her. - Why?
他们不肯说  总统先生  但说是紧急事件
They wouldn't tell me, sir, but they said it was urgent.
谢谢你  怀特
Thank you, Wyatt.
-卡莱拉局长  帕尔森国务卿  -总统先生
- Director Carrera. Secretary Paulsen. - Mr. President.
艾尔萨卡那边的调查有进展吗
Do we have an update on Al-Sakar?
没有  总统先生
No, sir.
我们要和你谈谈布拉德·威斯顿的事
We need to talk to you about Brad Weston.
好吧
Okay.
我们需要立即竭尽所能
We need to do everything we can
将他解救回国
to bring him back home immediately.
有消息要和我汇报吗
Is there something I should know?
总统先生  布拉德·威斯顿是我们的人
Sir, Brad Weston is one of ours.
他为中情局效力
He works for the CIA.
他是个间谍吗
He's a spy?
真不敢相信威斯顿教练竟然是间谍
I can't believe coach Weston is a spy.
他不是特工  只是个线人
He's not an officer. He's a resource.
作为世界一流的教练  他能见到
As a world-class coach, he gets into rooms
首相部长  寡头统治者和总统们
with ministers, oligarchs, presidents,
当他回到美国后
and when he returns to America,
会把他所见所闻分享给我们
he shares with us what he's seen and heard.
那禁药是怎么回事
But what about the drugs?
我们怀疑禁药是被人栽赃
We suspect they were planted
让俄国人有借口逮捕他
to give the Russians a pretense for his arrest.
他面临的最高刑罚是什么
What's the maximum sentence?
禁药的指控是终生监禁
For drugs? Life.
间谍活动的指控是死刑
For espionage? Death.
没我们帮忙的话  他再也走不出俄国
Without our help, he's never leaving Russia.
弗兰克酒吧
你们玩弹珠台的人是太老了玩不转电子游戏吗
So, are pinball people just too old to play video games?
我们是个濒危种族
We're a dying breed.
你想干什么  汉娜
What do you want, Hannah?
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
抱歉  帮不了你
Sorry. Can't do it.
联调局的人现在可不太受欢迎
FBI is persona non grata at the moment.
你老板从中情局手里抢走了纳萨尔
Your boss made a play to wrestle Nassar away from the CIA.
我们把这看成是私人恩怨
We take that personally.
好吧
All right.
看来我只好自己去找出卡特兰了
I'll just have to find Catalan myself.
你到底是从哪里听来的这个名字
Where the hell did you hear that name?
我用所有的数据库搜索过这个名字
I've run his name through every database.
什么都没有  这人是个幽灵
I got nothing. The guy's a ghost.
-如果中情局知道任何  -我就知道这个
- If the agency knows anything... - Here's what I know.
别插手这事
Stay out of it.
如果你去问其他人
And if you ask anyone else,
他们也会用不客气的方式这么告诉你
they'll tell you the same, just less politely.
那个人是个雇佣兵
The man's a mercenary...
也是一个叛国者
and a traitor.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
他是美国人吗
He's American?
等等  你就能告诉我这些吗
Wait a minute. That's all you're going to give me?
你觉得我没有帮你吗  汉娜
You don't think I'm helping you, Hannah?
不要管闲事
Walk away.
这是能给你的最好帮助
That's the best help anyone can give you.
先生  有很小的可能现在俄国人
Now, sir, in the off chance that the Russians
还不知道威斯顿是为我们效力
don't know that Weston is working for us,
我们不能和佩特洛夫大使
we can't say anything to Ambassador Petrov
说任何能让他暴露的话
that might compromise him.
我明白  在他们开口前不要承认任何事
I understand. Don't admit anything until they do.
佩特洛夫大使
Ambassador Petrov.
我是柯克曼总统
I'm President Kirkman.
希望能在更好的情况下和您会面  总统先生
I wish we were meeting under better circumstances, Mr. President.
很遗憾看到像威斯顿先生这样的传奇人物
It's a shame to see a legend like Mr. Weston
依靠欺诈的手段获胜
rely on such dishonest means to win.
我知道在你们国家针对这样的事情
Yes, I know - how stringent your country
有很严格的法律
has been about that sort of thing.
这在我们国家是一项严重的罪行
Well, this is a serious violation of our laws.
也许这就是你带了国防部代表
Maybe that's why you brought a representative
一起来参加这次会面的原因
from your Ministry of Defense to this meeting.
我没有想到一次个人药品违规
I didn't realize - that personal drug infractions
在俄国竟然是一项国家安全事件
was a matter of national security in Russia.
也许和你把中情局局长带来参会
Well, perhaps it's for the same reason
是同样的原因
you brought your head of CIA.
总统先生  是时候放下伪装了
Mr. President, it's time to drop the charade.
我们都知道布拉德·威斯顿是美国间谍
We both know Brad Weston is a U.S. Asset.
你和我对威斯顿教练的看法
You and I have a very different perspective
截然不同
on who Coach Weston is.
虽然这么说  我认为贵我两国
Having said that, I do believe that both our countries
应该尽量能够
would be served dealing with this
安静并且迅速的处理这个问题
as quietly and quickly as possible.
你想要什么
What do you want?
所有美国的核武器
All American nuclear weapons
都从土耳其的因切利克空军基地撤离
removed from Incirlik Air Base in Turkey.
这绝不可能
That will never happen.
那恐怕你们的间谍将会面对俄国法庭指控
Then I'm afraid your asset will face the Russian courts...
我国对于毒品和间谍的处理
which do not look kindly on either drugs...
都非常严重
or spies.
有了我国各州州长的全力配合
And with the cooperation of our nation's governors,
如你们所知  特殊国会选举
as you know, special congressional elections
已确认在本周晚些时候进行
have been confirmed for later this week.
好  接下来我只能回答几个问题
Okay, I just have time for a couple more questions.
-你来  -马吉德·纳萨尔在哪里
- Yeah. - Where is Majid Nassar?
为什么白宫
And why is the White House
对于他的所在地如此保密
being so secretive about his location?
谢莉  我们已经说过这个问题了
Shelly, we've been through this.
马吉德·纳萨尔被关押在一个秘密基地
Majid Nassar is at an undisclosed location
是为了他的安全
both for his protection
也是为了看守他的人的安全
and for the safety of those guarding him.
赛斯
Seth.
布拉德·威斯顿事件有新消息吗
Any update on Brad Weston?
总统已经和俄国大使
Yes. The president had a very productive meeting
进行了一次非常有效果的会谈
with the Russian ambassador,
我们希望这个情况
and we're hopeful that the situation
会被尽快解决  好吗
will be resolved soon, okay?
非常感谢大家
Thanks, everybody.
谢谢
Thank you.
丽萨
Lisa, hey.
这不是赛斯·怀特吗
Well, - if it isn't Seth Wright.
你是有信息给我  还是想我了
You have that comment for me, or you just miss me already?
我能私下和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you privately?
好
Yeah.
我有一件不太恰当并让我不舒服的事情
So, I have a very uncomfortable, likely inappropriate favor
想请你帮忙
to ask you.
好
Okay.
我希望你能把关于李奥的报道尽量往后拖
I need you to hold that story on Leo for as long as possible.
因为那是真的吗
'Cause it's true?
我没有这么说
I'm not saying that.
我知道这看起来并不太像是我在求你
Look, I know it doesn't look like I'm begging,
但是我拜托你
but this is me begging.
二十四小时
24 hours.
我只能拖我的主编这么久
I can't stall my editors any longer than that.
谢谢
Thank you.
你一定不会相信这个
You are not gonna believe this.
卡特兰是美国人
Catalan is an American.
我的线人说他是个叛国者
My contact says he's a traitor.
开什么玩笑
You've got to be kidding me.
怎么
What?
议员先生
Congressman.
威尔士探员
Agent Wells.
你好  很高兴再次见到你
Hello. It's good to see you again.
我也是
And you.
副局长  我能和你说两句吗
Deputy Director, may I have a moment?
当然
Sure.
威尔士探员  我们一会儿再继续谈
Agent Wells, we're get back to that in a second.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
失陪
Excuse me.
请坐
Have a seat.
这些意外会面就要成习惯了
You know, these unexpected meetings are becoming a habit.
是啊  抱歉
Yeah. I'm sorry.
我知道你忙着调查纳萨尔的案子
I know you have your hands full with the Nassar investigation.
除此之外
And on top of that,
我知道联调局必须审查我是否胜任副总统一职
I understand the FBI's been asked to vet me for VP.
所以让我为联调局节省些资源吧
So let me save the bureau some resources.
七年的州纳税申报单和联邦纳税申报单
Seven years -- state and federal tax returns.
兵役记录和退役批文
Military service records and discharge papers.
近期的医疗检查
Latest medical exams.
还有其他一些
A few other things in there
我觉得你可能会感兴趣的事
I thought you might be interested in.
而这些文件
And these documents --
有没有可能和我们自己找到的不符呢
Any chance they won't match what we can find ourselves?
除非我妻子  律师
Not unless my wife, lawyer,
以及内科医生一起密谋陷害我
and internist are conspiring against me.
你明白我们会继续进行审查吧
You do understand that we will continue with our own vetting?
我正希望这样
I'd expect no less.
你也懂的
You know how it is.
白纸黑字
What's on the paper,
都是些我们想让人知道的事
that tells a story that we want to tell.
但文件上没有记录的
But what's not on the paper --
才是人们牢记的事
That's what people remember.
我们留下的印象
The impressions we leave behind --
这些我们也会调查
Now, we search for those, too...
因为那才是衡量一个人的真正标准
'cause, you see, that's the true measure of a man.
当然
Of course.
我想我们最不希望看到的是
I think the last thing that either of us wants
由不当的人来掌权
is the wrong person in office.
我向你保证
I promise you --
联调局是不会让这种事发生的
The bureau ain't gonna let that happen.
副局长
Deputy Director...
谢谢你
thank you.
议员
Congressman.
他来干什么
What the hell was that?
你觉得呢  说了一堆废话
What the hell you think it was? A bunch of B.S.
他就这样走进来
The guy's gonna walk in here
没人要求就自觉地把十年来的文件
and voluntarily give us 10 years of papers
都交给我们吗
that no one asked for?
他为什么如此着急这么做
Now, why would he be so eager to do that?
因为他有所隐瞒
Because he's got something to hide.
今晨早些时候  抵达莫斯科时
Early this morning, upon arrival in Moscow,
海关人员在我的手提箱里
customs agents discovered
找到二十小瓶人体生长激素
20 vials of HGH in my suitcase.
我很清楚这些药物在俄罗斯是非法的
I was well-aware that these were illegal in Russia.
但是我的压力不小  并且必须要保证
But I was under pressure to make sure
我们的表演要在最高水准
that we were performing at the highest level.
非常抱歉  我违反了
I am very sorry for my transgressions
俄罗斯政府的法规
against the Russian government.
俄罗斯现在要加倍严格处理
Well, the Russians are doubling down.
强迫美国一代传奇认罪吗
By coercing a confession from an American legend.
我们必须阻止这事  我只是不知道该怎么做
We've got to stop this. I just don't know how.
总统先生  我有办法把布拉德·威斯顿带回来
Sir, I think I know a way to get Brad Weston back.
您是篮球迷吗
Are you a basketball fan?
篮球和这件事有什么关系
What does basketball got to do with this?
去年  华盛顿奇才队
Last year, the Washington Wizards
与雷霆队交换控球后卫
traded for the Thunder's point guard.
但是奇才队没有雷霆队想要的球员
But the Wizards didn't have a player the Thunder wanted,
所以他们得去第三支球队找
so they had to find a third team who did.
女人才是真球迷啊
Apparently, men don't own sports.
不  这个办法很好  三方交换
No, this is good. A three-way trade.
找找俄罗斯想要的
Find out what the Russians want.
找到有能力交换的国家
Find the country that's got it.
是  总统先生
Yes, sir.
艾丽克斯·柯克曼
Alex Kirkman.
你现在富贵了嘛
You did well for yourself.
你就不怎么样了
Can't say the same for you.
十八年了
18 years.
你还是和从前一样漂亮
Beautiful as ever.
你想怎样  杰弗里
What do you want, Jeffrey?
你总是很会算计
You always had an angle.
是的  因为很多人很会算计
Yeah, I made a lot of money
我才赚了很多钱
for a lot of people working an angle.
真逗
That's funny.
你永远分不清
You never could tell the difference
侮辱和赞美之间的区别
between an insult and a compliment.
但你不是来追忆往事的吧
But you're not here to reminisce, are you?
不是
No, I am not.
我是来明确地告诉你
I am here to tell you in no uncertain terms
离我儿子远点
to stay away from my son.
-你儿子  -是的
- Your son? - Yeah.
我在电视上看到你了
I saw you on TV.
你  总统和你的家人
You, the President, your family.
看看里奥  看看他的眼睛和下巴
And looking at Leo, his eyes, his chin,
我只能想到  他有可能是我儿子
all I could think was, "Wow. He could be my son."
再看看你
And looking at you now,
我看得出  你也不确定
I can tell -- you're not sure either.
不是
Oh, no.
他有父亲
He has a father.
我知道
Oh, I know.
是有权提前释放我的人
A man with the authority to release me with time served.
你真是一点都没变
You really haven't changed at all.
看看我现在在哪  艾丽克斯
Look at where I am, Alex.
要么你帮我离开这里
So, either you help me get out of here,
要么我就把事情昭告天下
or I tell the world my story.
部长女士  我想感谢你的尽职工作
Madam Secretary, I want to thank you for your diligence.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
失陪一下
Excuse me for one second.
当然  总统先生
Of course, sir.
我们找到了俄罗斯人想要的
We've identified something the Russians want.
从沙特阿拉伯那边
From the Saudis.
我们必须快速行动  总统先生
But we have to act fast, sir.
干得好
Good work.
-去做准备  -是的  总统先生
- Set it up. - Yes, sir.
麦克利什来这里真是勇气可嘉
Took some nerve for MacLeish to show up here.
可不是吗
Tell me about it.
你看他的文件时  有什么发现
But when you look at his file, what do you notice?
-彼得·麦克利什很无趣  -是的
- That Peter MacLeish is boring. - Right.
他以此来证明
And that's his proof
他就是个模范公民
that he's some exemplary human being.
我们知道他牵扯进了这事
Well, we know he's mixed up in this,
所以这是不可能的
so there goes that.
是的  但问题是纳萨尔不知道他是谁
Yeah, but the problem is, Nassar has no idea who he is.
我们怎么才能把
So how do we connect
这个当过俄勒冈州三任议员的人
a three-time congressman from Oregon
和北非的圣战恐怖组织联系在一起呢
with a Jihadist from North Africa?
也许卡特兰就是关键
Maybe Catalan is the connection.
是的  可我们不知道卡特兰是谁
Yeah, but we still don't know who Catalan is.
亲爱的  怎么了
Hi, hon. What's up?
卢克没从校车上下来
Luke never got off the bus.
我去了学校
I came to the school.
他也没在那
He's not here either.
好吧  你到处去找他了吗
All right, well, did you look everywhere for him?
棒球场找过吗  报警了吗
Check the baseball field? Or did you call the police?
没有  我直接打给你了
No, I called you.
伊薇特  挂掉电话
Okay, Yvette, hang up the phone
然后报警
and call the police.
我去学校找你
I'm gonna meet you at the school.
怎么了
What's going on?
我儿子没回家
My son never made it home.
我得走了
I got to go.
佩特洛夫大使
Ambassador Petrov?
在总统办公室等你
Waiting in the Oval.
沙特的大使在罗斯福厅  总统先生
The Saudi ambassador's in the Roosevelt Room, sir.
知道了
Got it.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
祝你好运
Good luck.
大使先生
Mr. Ambassador.
谢谢你能这么快来见我
Thank you for making it here on such short notice.
请坐
Please.
艾哈迈德国王一直都乐于帮助美国朋友
King Ahmed is always eager to help his American friends.
那我就开门见山了
Well, then I'll get straight to the point.
我想提一项协议
I would like to propose a deal.
协议
A deal?
交换威斯顿先生吗
In exchange for Mr. Weston?
-是的  -什么内容
- Yes. - And what is this?
我们愿意把被联调局逮捕的
We are willing to return four Saudi nationals
四名沙特国民交还给你们
who were arrested by the FBI
他们对得州的一家石油公司
for committing industrial espionage
进行了工业间谍活动
against a Texas oil company.
这是你们的说法
Or so you claim.
无论怎样  你愿不愿意让他们释放
Nevertheless, would you like to see them free
今晚就飞回国
and flying home tonight?
那你想要什么回报
And what would you like in return?
你们去年夏天在利雅得抓到的俄罗斯特工
The Russian agent you picked up in Riyadh last summer.
特工
An agent?
那个人是去出差的普通公民
This man was a private citizen on a business trip.
沙特方面可不是这么说的
Not according to the Saudis.
他是联邦安全局的卧底特工
He was a deep-cover operative for the FSB.
那沙特想从我们这得到什么
And what would the Saudis like from us?
什么也不要
Absolutely nothing.
那俄罗斯想从我们这得到什么
And what do the Russians want from us?
什么也不要
Absolutely nothing.
Nothing?
什么也不要
只要俄罗斯能接回他们的人
As long as the Russians get their officer back,
我们也会交还你们的人
we will return your people to you.
总统先生  我不得不说
I must say, Mr. President...
这是个非同寻常的提议
This is a very unusual proposal.
现在是非同寻常的时期
These are very unusual times.
我们可以接回我们的公民
So, we get our citizens back.
我们可以接回我们的同志
And we get our comrade home.
而一名美国英雄
And an American hero
也可以回家  一个感恩的国家
gets to return home to a grateful nation.
大使先生
Mr. Ambassador...
可以达成协议吗
do we have an agreement?
三方跨国间谍交换
A transnational three-way spy trade.
-干得漂亮  总统先生  -还没成呢
- Well done, sir. - Nothing's done yet.
而且很容易功亏一篑
And it's not gonna take much for it to all fall apart.
所以我需要你们盯好这事
So I need you both to stay on top of it.
我要回住处见艾丽克斯
I need to see Alex over at the residence.
好的
Yes, sir.
因为他  我觉得有必要
He actually makes me reconsider
重新考虑一下我对死刑的看法了
my position on the death penalty.
他想怎么样
What did he want?
你代表他联系假释委员会  他就不再纠缠了
He'll back off if you call the parole board on his behalf.
结束刑期  提前释放
Time served, early release.
是的
Yeah.
如果不  他就会跟记者说
If not, he talks to the reporter.
简直是敲诈
It's blackmail.
一个机会主义者掌握了有力的威胁
An opportunist with a credible threat
是一件很危险的事
is a dangerous thing.
我以为不用再应付这事了
I never thought I'd be dealing with this again --
无论李奥是不是我的亲生儿子
whether or not Leo was mine.
我都不记得上次想这事是什么时候了
I can't even remember the last time I thought about it.
我一直觉得他就是我亲儿子
I guess I always figured he had to be,
因为我非常爱他
because I loved him so much.
他就是你的儿子
He is yours.
汤姆  他永远都是你儿子
Come on, Tom. He will always be yours.
很快  我们的儿子和整个国家的人
Pretty soon, our son and this country
可能就不这么认为了
might not feel the same way.
你说得对
You were right.
什么
About what?
你当时怀上李奥的时候
When you got pregnant with Leo,
你就担心时间对不对
you were worried about the timing of everything.
你想要知道他的父亲是谁
You wanted to know who the father was.
你让我去做检测
You asked me to get tested.
我拒绝了
I said no.
我们不需要
We didn't need to.
我甚至以为自己很高尚
I even acted noble about it,
像是在保护李奥一样
like I was protecting Leo somehow.
可事实是  我是在保护我自己
Truth is, I was protecting myself.
我非常爱你
I loved you so much.
我知道我想要的是什么
I knew what I wanted,
我对任何会影响到我们的事
and I was scared to death of anything
感到非常害怕
that could jeopardize that.
汤姆
Tom...
李奥有权知道他的亲生父亲是谁
Leo has every right to know who his real father is...
即使那个人不是我
even if it's not me.
什么事
Yeah?
好的
Okay.
他们需要我去指挥中心
They need me down in Command Ops.
-伊薇特  -杰森
- Yvette. - Jason.
你找到他了吗
Did you find him?
他们搜索了整座学校
They searched the whole school.
-他不在这  -好的  冷静
- He is not here. - Okay, calm down.
你有叫他们去漫画店找吗
All right, did you tell them about the comic-book store?
是的  我跟他们说了
Yes, I told them - about the comic-book store.
去公园找过吗
What about -- What about the park?
-没错  -我们的儿子在少棒联盟打球
- The park, yes... - Our son plays Little League...
他和朋友经常去公园玩
and his friends that he hangs out with.
就在钱柏林公园
...over at the park on Chamberlain.
副局长
Deputy Director...
大多数情况都是这样的
you know - most situations like this,
孩子根本不知道有人在找他
the kid turns up in a few hours,
几个小时候后自己就回来了
doesn't even know anyone's been looking for him.
这次不一样  他是我儿子
Except this time, it's my son.
你先回家
You go home.
你回去等卢克好吗
You wait on Luke, okay?
随时等着电话
Stay by your phone.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我去找我们的儿子
I'm gonna find our son.
总统先生  间谍交换就要开始了
Sir, the spy exchange is imminent.
三架飞机即将着陆
All three planes are about to land --
伦敦  莫斯科  利雅得
London, Moscow, Riyadh.
-终于等到了  -总统先生
- Finally. - Sir?
这是我们今天收到的第一个好消息
First good news we've had all day.
到哪里了
Where are we?
总统先生  前两架飞机已经抵达目的地
Sir, first two planes have arrived.
莫斯科和利雅得的同僚已向我们确认
We've gotten confirmation from our people in Moscow and Riyadh.
正在等待伦敦方面的消息
We're waiting on London.
威斯顿所乘的飞机已经着陆
Weston's plane has landed.
这位是大使馆的二把手
The Embassy Deputy Chief of Mission, DCM --
等他迎接威斯顿时  就有现场视频信号了
We'll have a live feed when he greets Weston.
那些人是俄罗斯的驾驶员
Those are the Russian pilots.
威斯顿现在该下飞机了
Weston should be stepping off now.
再问一遍
Ask him again.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我需要立即答复
I want confirmation now.
总统先生
Mr. President...
布拉德·威斯顿根本没在那架飞机上
it appears Brad Weston never got on that plane.
杰森  找到他了吗
Jason, did you find him?
还没
No.
汉娜  问你一个问题
Hannah, let me ask you a question.
如果这不是巧合怎么办
What if this isn't a coincidence?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
麦克利什刚来过我的办公室
I mean MacLeish shows up at my office,
接着我儿子就失踪了
and then my son goes missing.
杰森  别这样
Jason, stop.
你是不是跟我说过
No. Aren't you the one
国会大厦遇袭那晚
that told me the night of the attack,
麦克利什的孩子被人带走了
MacLeish's kid was taken, right?
不  是他的妻子在商场找不着女儿了
No, I told you that his wife may have lost her at the mall.
这是两回事
That's not the same thing.
我们并不能确定就是一样的情况
We don't know that this is what we're dealing with.
那又怎么知道不是呢
Well, how do we know it's not?
我是说
I mean, this...
都怪我
this is all my fault.
听我说  我们并肩作战
Hey, listen to me. We're in this together.
好的  我这就去
All right, I'm on it.
他怎么会没在那架飞机上
How the hell - was he not on that plane?
俄罗斯仍然扣押着他吗
So, what, the Russians are still holding him?
总统先生  我暂时无法给您答复
Sir, I can't answer that yet.
但我向您保证我们会派所有人去寻找他
But I can assure you that we have everyone looking for him.
直接传输过来
Transmit it directly.
我们获取了一个来自那里的数据加密包
We've got the right - encryption packet in place.
总统先生  非常抱歉
Mr. President, my apologies.
我们的特工需要时间进行信息确认
Our agents needed time to confirm.
请您看一下这个
You need to see this.
放到大屏幕上
Put it up on the screen.
那是什么
What am I looking at?
右边的是维克多·米什金
The one on the right is Viktor Mishkin.
莫斯科驻派组确认他是
Our Moscow station identified him
俄罗斯联邦安全局的一名上校
as a Russian FSB captain,
是招募外国间谍最多的人
and the top recruiter of foreign assets.
左边的这个人是谁
And the man on his left?
他就是布拉德·威斯顿  总统先生
That's Brad Weston, sir.
不知为何他人还在俄罗斯
However it happened, he's still in Russia.
几分钟前他与他们通过情报
He made contact with their intelligence a few minutes ago.
我们认为另一个人是威斯顿的联系人和上级
We believe the other man is Weston's contact and handler.
上级
Handler?
我们现在知道他为什么没有上那架飞机了
We now know why he didn't get on that plane.
妈的
Son of a bitch.
布拉德·威斯顿是双面间谍
Brad Weston is a double agent.
对于间谍来说  真的很容易找到你
You know, for a spook, you're pretty easy to track.
你为什么来这  该说的我都说了
Why are you here? I meant what I said.
我不会帮你的  你不要插手此事了
I'm not helping you. Stay out of it.
我做不到
I can't.
我需要你手上关于卡特兰的所有线索
I need - what you have on Catalan.
蒂姆
Tim...
拜托
please.
我没时间了
I'm out of time.
汉娜  我不想你受伤
Hannah, I don't want to see you get hurt.
有我爱的人遇到麻烦了
There are people that I love that are in trouble.
我不在乎我会面对什么
I don't care what happens to me.
我在乎的是他们的安危
I care what happens to them.
求你了
Please.
我看看吧
Let me see what I can do.
-总统先生  -佩特洛夫大使到了
- Mr. President. - Ambassador Petrov.
谢谢你  怀特
Thank you, Wyatt.
大使先生  您今天捉弄了我
Mr. Ambassador, you played me today.
威斯顿为中情局效力的十年当中
During the 10 years that Mr. Weston worked with the CIA,
他成为了专案官员
he gained access to case officers.
那就是一座秘密宝藏  如果你愿意这样说
A clandestine treasure trove, if you will.
现在  它是您的了
Now it's yours.
恭喜您
Congratulations.
俄罗斯是一个自由的国度  总统先生
Russia is a free country, Mr. President.
也许威斯顿先生只是选择留在莫斯科
Perhaps Mr. Weston simply chose to remain in Moscow.
如果您有玩国际象棋
When you've been at the game of international chess
超过一个月的话  您就会明白这些事了
for more than a month, you'll understand these things.
我今天算是受教了
Well, I may have been in over my head today,
但我向您保证  我很擅长学习
but I promise you -- I'm a quick study.
国际象棋中有个道理我还是懂的
And the one thing - that I do know about chess
没有什么比兵更具杀伤力
is that there is nothing more dangerous
兵走到底线就能变成皇后
than a pawn - that thinks it's a queen.
保重  大使先生
Take care, Mr. Ambassador.
总统先生
Mr. President.
放松点  你还有十九个小时呢
Relax. You still have 19 hours left.
我想我不需要了
Yeah, I don't think I need them.
你有定论了吗
You have that comment for me?
没  但有其他东西给你  独家新闻
No. I have something else -- an exclusive.
我已经有一个独家新闻了
Well, I've already got an exclusive.
没错  我打赌你更想要这一个
Yeah, I'm betting - you're gonna want this one.
-为什么这么说  -因为它不是谣言
- Why is that? - It's not gossip.
我不是八卦专栏作家  赛斯
I am not a gossip columnist, Seth.
我在整理一个男人的政绩概况
I'm building - a political profile of a man
这个国家都极度想进一步了解他
this country is desperate to know more about --
你的上司
your boss.
但知道你怎么看待我的也好
But it's good to know that's how you see me.
丽莎  我不是这样看你的
Lisa, - that's not how I see you.
你可以刊登李奥的那篇文章
Look, you can publish the piece on Leo.
我只是觉得你不应该
I just don't think you should.
柯克曼总统是好人
President Kirkman is a good man.
他们家庭和睦
They're a great family.
这份工作不是他自己要求的  但现在他身在其位
He didn't ask for this job, but now he's got it,
所有人都针对他
and everyone's gunning for him.
李奥17岁了
And Leo's 17.
我觉得不应当让他的生活
I don't think he deserves to have his life
放在头版被人议论
analyzed on the front page.
所以你的独家呢
So, what's the exclusive?
内部消息  第一手资料
Inside information, first-person account,
总统如何谈判释放
of how the president negotiated for the release
美国英雄
of an American hero,
却发现他表里不一的真面目
only to discover he's not who he seems.
你有什么关于威斯顿的消息
What do you have on Weston?
我们达成协议  我就告诉你
Let's make a deal, and I'll tell you.
-谢谢  怀特  -当然  总统先生
- Thank you, Wyatt. - Of course, sir.
谢谢你
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
天色不早了  你们俩不回家的吗
It's late. Don't you two ever go home?
下一任总统上台我们就回家
We'll go home when the next president takes office.
想要提前开始明天的工作吗
Want to get a head start on tomorrow's work?
反正你也都没睡多久
Since you haven't been sleeping much anyway.
拿来看看
Show me what you got.
早晨的安全简报后
After your morning security briefing,
你将与国家经济委员会主席见面
you'll be meeting the director of the National Economic Council.
然后呢  还有别的吗
And? What else?
麦克利什  总统先生
MacLeish, sir.
他怎么了
What about him?
先生  你们俩既然如此合拍
Well, sir, we've been thinking since you two hit it off so well,
也许我们应该正式宣布
maybe we should make it official.
媒体已经推测
The press is already speculating
他会是你的副总统
he might be your vice president.
随着下周国会选举的到来...
And with the congressional elections coming up next week...
这个国家需要一些好消息  你觉得呢
The country could use some good news. Don't you think?
我决定等着联调局的消息
I've decided to wait to hear what the FBI has to say.
如果今天的事情有任何教育意义
If today's taught me anything,
那就是你对任何人都不够了解
it's that you can't know enough about a person.
亚伦  副局长亚特伍德那里
Aaron, any news yet from Deputy Director Atwood
有任何杀害纳萨尔凶手的消息吗
on who might have killed Nassar?
没有  先生  我整个下午都在联系他
No, sir. I've been trying to get ahold of him all afternoon.
他的秘书说他离开了办公室
His secretary said he's been out of the office
处理私事
on personal business.
私事
Personal business?
在谋杀调查期间吗
During a murder investigation?
-我会跟进的  总统先生  -很好
- I’ll keep on top of him, sir. - Good.
我们现在最不需要的事
The last thing we need is the world
就是发现纳萨尔死了  但不知道凶手是谁
to find out that Nassar is dead and we don't know who did it.
总统令
Presidential order --
你们俩  立刻回家睡一觉
Both of you, go home, get some sleep.
-感谢你们做的一切  -谢谢  总统先生
- Thanks for everything. - Thank you, sir.
进来
Yeah?
怎么了
What's up?
只想说声晚安
Ju-- Just wanted to say good night.
好
Okay.
怎么了
What?
你为什么这样看着我
Why are you looking at me like that?
我不知道
I don't know. It...
过去的六周发生了很多事
A lot's happened in this last six weeks.
我觉得我见不到你也跟你说不上话
I feel like I haven't seen you or talked to you.
一切都好吗
Is everything all right?
还好  我
Yeah. I...
我只想告诉你我爱你
I just wanted to tell you that I love you.
好
Yeah.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
晚安
Good night.
中央情报单位
罪犯调查档案
中央情报报告
内斯特·罗萨诺  化名卡特兰
姓名  内斯特·罗萨诺
化名  卡特兰
饭点
Chow time.
你们得等着了
Guess your guy will have to wait.
教练
Coach!
你看到我儿子了吗
Have you seen my son?
快接
Come on.
杰森  是汉娜  打给我
Jason, it's Hannah. Call me back.
我知道是谁杀了纳萨尔
I know who killed Nassar.
卢克
Luke?!
亚特伍德先生
Mr. Atwood.
我注意到你儿子今天没来训练
I noticed your son didn't show up for practice.
你见过他吗
Have you seen him?
我跟你保证  卢克没事
I can assure you, Luke is fine.
实际上他是我知道唯一一个
In fact, he's the only kid I know
喜欢咖啡味冰激凌的孩子
who likes coffee ice cream.
我的儿子在哪里
Where's my son?
Where is my son?
深呼吸  杰森
Deep breath, Jason.
好好想想
Think it through.
我要是出了任何事  你看到的下一张照片
Anything happens to me, and the next photo you'll see
就是头上中枪的卢克
is Luke with a bullet in his brain.
我知道你爱你的家人
I know you love your family,
要是卢克出了什么事就太凄惨了
and it would be a tragedy if something happened to Luke...
或者是伊薇特
or to Yvette...
在你埋葬儿子之后
Sometime after you buried your son.
你伤害我的家人  我发誓
You hurt my family, I promise you --
我会杀了你
I will kill you
还有和你一伙的人
and whoever the hell you're working with.
只要你照我说的去做
Your son will be safe
你的儿子就会没事的
as long as you do everything I tell you to do,
不如从最显而易见的开始
starting with the obvious.
如果你对任何人提起这次见面  卢克就会死
Tell anyone about this encounter and Luke dies.
你想要什么
What do you want?
跟总统预约会面
You're going to make an appointment with the president.
当你跟柯克曼面对面时
And when you're face-to-face with Kirkman,
你要按照我的指令行事
you will do exactly as I instruct.
我会联系你的
I'll be in touch.
■
一键收藏网盘资源
生活大爆炸 吸血鬼日记
西部世界 谍网 超女
美剧资源应有尽有
扫码即刻关注
Zimuzu特别推荐
■
马上关注微信人人美剧（rrmjapp）